[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question_text": "What is 2 + 2?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
        "answer_key": "4",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question_text": "Which of these are programming languages?",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question_type": "multi_select",
        "options": ["Python", "HTML", "JavaScript", "CSS"],
        "answer_key": ["Python", "JavaScript"],
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Computer Science"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question_text": "Multiples of 3",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "multiple_select",
        "options": ["2", "3", "4", "6"],
        "answer_key": ["3", "6"],
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question_text": "Explain the concept of gravity.",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question_type": "long_answer",
        "options": [],
        "answer_key": "Gravity is a force that attracts two bodies towards each other.",
        "marks": 5,
        "topic": "Physics"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question_text": "What is square root of 49?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["2", "7", "8", "5"],
        "answer_key": "7",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question_text": "What country has the most islands?",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["canada", "sweden", "russia", "japan"],
        "answer_key": "sweden",
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question_text": "Who was the dictator that led Italy into WW2?",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["Mussolini", "Hitler", "Goebbels", "Churchill"],
        "answer_key": "Mussolini",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "History"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question_text": "Whivh of the below are not types of watches?",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question_type": "multiple_select",
        "options": ["Pocket", "Mechanical", "Artificial", "Quantum"],
        "options": ["Pocket", "Mechanical", "Artificial", "Quantum"],
        "answer_key": ["Artificial","Quantum"]
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "General Knowledge"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question_text": "Describe what is meant by perestroika",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question_type": "long_answer",
        "options": [],
        "answer_key": "The literal meaning of perestroika is restructuring, referring to the restructuring of the political economy of the Soviet Union, in an attempt to end the Era of Stagnation.",
        "marks": "5",
        "topic": "History"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question_text": "What square root of -1?",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["i", "1", "x", "0.5"],
        "answer_key": "i",
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question_text": "What is the only city located in both Europe and Asia?",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["Istanbul", "Medina", "Moscow", "Kyiv"],
        "answer_key": "Istanbul",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "Geography"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question_text": "What is the period of time called where the USA and the USSR engaged in political rivalry from 1945-1991?",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "question_type": "long_anwser",
        "options": [],
        "answer_key": "Cold War",
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "History"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question_text": "What is the famous venue where the Mosconi Cup took place in 2022?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "long_answer",
        "options": [],
        "answer_key": "Alexandra Palace",
        "marks": "4",
        "topic": "General Knowledge"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question_text": "What is the possible values of x? x(x-8)(x-4)",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question_type": "multiple_select",
        "options": ["8", "0", "5", "4"],
        "answer_key": ["4", "8", "8"],
        "marks": "3",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question_text": "What year did the most watched football game take place?",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["2022", "2018", "2020", "1966"],
        "answer_key": "2022",
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question_text": "What is 29 + 7?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["36", "35", "37", "20"],
        "answer_key": "36",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question_text": "What is 58-19?",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["39", "30", "47", "53"],
        "answer_key": "39",
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question_text": "What is 2 to the power of 10?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["256", "3000", "512", "1024"],
        "answer_key": "1024",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question_text": "How many ways can you write a string using all of the letters abcde?",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["120", "30", "42", "58"],
        "answer_key": "120",
        "marks": "3",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question_text": "What is 7x4?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["5", "74", "0", "28"],
        "answer_key": "28",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question_text": "Why isnt any number actually random?",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question_type": "long_answer",
        "options": [],
        "answer_key": "computers produce random numbers using mathematical formulas so essentialy no number is actually random",
        "marks": "3",
        "topic": "Computer Science"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question_text": "What country uses bitcoin as a legal currency?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "long_answer",
        "options": [],
        "answer_key": "El Salvador",
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Computer Science"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question_text": "What is the name of the decoder that helped Britain win WW2?",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question_type": "long_answer",
        "options": [],
        "answer_key": "Enigma Machine",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "Computer Science"
    },
        {
        "id": 24,
        "question_text": "Who made the first automatic digital computer?",
        "difficulty": "Hard",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["Alan Turing", "Charles Babbage", "Von Neumann", "Oppenheimer"],
        "answer_key": "Charles Babbage",
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Computer Science"
    },
        {
        "id": 25,
        "question_text": "What is the 74 digit of pi?",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["5", "4", "0", "8"],
        "answer_key": "8",
        "marks": "4",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
        {
        "id": 26,
        "question_text": "Who are the best computer science teachers at WBGS?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "multiple_select",
        "options": ["Mr Carr", "Mr Adcock"],
        "answer_key": ["Mr Carr", "Mr Adcock"],
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Computer Science"
    },
        {
        "id": 27,
        "question_text": "What is e?",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question_type": "long_answer",
        "options": [],
        "answer_key": "The exponential constant is a significant mathematical constant and is denoted by the symbol 'e'. It is approximately equal to 2.718. ",
        "marks": "3",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
        {
        "id": 28,
        "question_text": "What is the 5th root of 243?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["45", "3", "0", "98932"],
        "answer_key": "3",
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
        {
        "id": 29,
        "question_text": "What is 5x2?",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["5", "74", "10", "28"],
        "answer_key": "10",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "Maths"
    },
        {
        "id": 30,
        "question_text": "What is the programming language used to code in the eteherum blockchain?",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["Solidarity", "Python", "Java", "C++"],
        "answer_key": "Solidarity",
        "marks": "2",
        "topic": "Computer science"
    },
        {
        "id": 31,
        "question_text": "What is 4x20?",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question_type": "multiple_choice",
        "options": ["80", "74", "0", "28"],
        "answer_key": "80",
        "marks": "1",
        "topic": "Maths"
    }
    
]
